this is just a quick video about how to
synchronize your panes so that you can
have the same thing happen in the same
directory I mean in this in all three
different panes uh with with uh t-m a
lot of people already know this so this
is uh so to to do it you need to do you
know colon set sync tab on and then I'll
synchronize your pains and then when you
want to actually do something
individually to each one
uh you can do set synchronization off so
you just need to make a specific change
to this one and then you can go back to
it pretty easily you can of course map
that to something I don't because I
don't use this enough to do that um but
if you did you can make it into make it
into a quick key if you want to um if
you have suggestions about what your
favorite key is for synchronized panes
and you've actually bound that to a
hotkey please let me know maybe I'll use
your idea